[{"answer": "Dad, I cant believe you lost your job.  What are you going to do", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I know, I know.  I dont know what Ill do, Kay.  I guess Ill have to figure somethin", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Dad, I cant believe you lost your job.  What are you going to do", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " I just cant believe that theyd fire you after you worked so hard for the compan", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " I know, I know.  I dont know what Ill do, Kay.  I guess Ill have to figure somethin", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " It wasnt that much of a shock to me, with all of these young kids moving up th", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I just cant believe that theyd fire you after you worked so hard for the compan", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " What do you mean, Dad", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 28, "question": " It wasnt that much of a shock to me, with all of these young kids moving up th", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Well, Im 58 now, which is considered too old to be a good employee anymore", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 29, "question": " What do you mean, Dad", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Is that why they said they fired you?  Because of your age", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Well, Im 58 now, which is considered too old to be a good employee anymore", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " No, no.  They cant openly fire someone because of their age, thats illegal.  The", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Is that why they said they fired you?  Because of your age", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " I dont understand.  Why would a company want to fire people with years o", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 42, "question": " No, no.  They cant openly fire someone because of their age, thats illegal.  The", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Thats how it is nowadays.  Companies think that youthful employees will do ", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": " I dont understand.  Why would a company want to fire people with years o", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " That just seems so wrong.  If age discrimination is illegal, isnt there somethin", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Thats how it is nowadays.  Companies think that youthful employees will do ", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " You know, I was just talking to my friend Mark--whos a lawyer--about that.  H", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " That just seems so wrong.  If age discrimination is illegal, isnt there somethin", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 65, "question": " You know, I was just talking to my friend Mark--whos a lawyer--about that.  H", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Yep.  Thats what he said", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Have there been a lot of successful lawsuits against age discrimination", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Yep.  Thats what he said", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Mark says there have.  More people are speaking out if they think they hav", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Have there been a lot of successful lawsuits against age discrimination", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Well, what are you going to do", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Mark says there have.  More people are speaking out if they think they hav", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " I havent quite decided.  Im going to read more about this age discrimination ac", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Well, what are you going to do", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Im so worried.  I can give you the little bit of money I have in my savings account", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 81, "question": " I havent quite decided.  Im going to read more about this age discrimination ac", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Thats nice of you sweetheart, but dont do that.  Well figure something out.  Wel", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Im so worried.  I can give you the little bit of money I have in my savings account", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Could you get another job", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thats nice of you sweetheart, but dont do that.  Well figure something out.  Wel", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Id like to, but at my age, its too late to start down another career path.  No on", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Could you get another job", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Oh, I see  I guess thats the problem", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Id like to, but at my age, its too late to start down another career path.  No on", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Im meeting with Mark again on Friday, so Ill keep you in the loop about what", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Oh, I see  I guess thats the problem", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " OK, Dad.  If theres anything you want me to do, let me know", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Im meeting with Mark again on Friday, so Ill keep you in the loop about what", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Thanks, honey.  I will.  Anyways, I need to get my mind off this for a little while", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 102, "question": " OK, Dad.  If theres anything you want me to do, let me know", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 106, "question": " Thanks, honey.  I will.  Anyways, I need to get my mind off this for a little while", "qSentId": 105},{"answer": " OK, grab your coat and lets go", "docId": "01-07", "aSentId": 107, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 106}]
